https://gelleradvisors.com/california-residents-privacy-policy/

Home > CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS PRIVACY POLICY
This California
Privacy Policy describes Geller & Company LLC’s and Geller Advisors LLC’s (“Geller
,” “we,” “us,” or “our”) practices regarding the collection, use, and
disclosure of the personal information of California residents (“Consumers”),
describes the rights of Consumers under the California Consumer Privacy Act of
2018 (“CCPA”), and explains how Consumers may contact Geller to exercise those
rights. This policy only applies to the personal information of Consumers
(i.e., California residents).
Consumer Rights
This section
describes certain rights of Consumers under CCPA. For information on how Consumers
may contact us to exercise these rights, please see the section below entitled,
“How to Submit a Request.”
Right to Know
A Consumer has the right to request that a business disclose what personal information it collects, uses, discloses or sells. Specifically, a Consumer may request that a business that collects personal information about the Consumer disclose to the Consumer the following:
The categories of personal information it has collected about that Consumer;The categories of sources from which the personal information is collected;The business or commercial purpose for collecting or selling personal information;The categories of third parties with whom the business shares personal information;The specific pieces of personal information it has collected about that Consumer.
A Consumer may
request that a business that sells the Consumer’s personal information, or that
discloses it for a business purpose, disclose to that Consumer:
The categories of personal information that the business collected about the Consumer;The categories of personal information that the business sold about the Consumer and the categories of third parties to whom the personal information was sold, by category or categories of personal information for each third party to whom the personal information was sold;The categories of personal information that the business disclosed about the Consumer for a business purpose.
Right to Request
Deletion
A Consumer has the
right to request that a business delete any personal information about the Consumer
which the business has collected from the Consumer. If it is necessary for us
to maintain the personal information for certain purposes, we are not required
to comply with your deletion request. If we determine that we will not delete
your personal information when you request us to do so, we will inform you and
tell you why we are not deleting it.
Right to Opt-Out of Sale of Personal Information
Geller  does not and will not sell Consumer personal
information. While we do not sell Consumers’ personal information, pursuant to
applicable law, you may request that your information not be sold in the future
by going visiting the following webpage:
https://gelleradvisors.com/personal-data-inquiry-form/
No Discrimination
A Consumer has the
right not to be discriminated against because the Consumer exercised any of the
Consumer’s rights under the CCPA. [We may charge a Consumer a different price
or rate, or provide a different level or quality of goods or services to the Consumer,
if that difference is reasonably related to the value provided to the Consumer
by the Consumer’s data.]
How to Submit a
Request
To exercise the
rights described above, you must submit a verifiable Consumer request to us by
contacting us through one of the following methods:
Visiting the following webpage: https://gelleradvisors.com/personal-data-inquiry-form/ Calling the following toll-free number: 833-978-2139
You may submit a
request as frequently as you would like, but we are not required to respond to
requests to provide personal information to you more than twice in any 12-month
period.
To submit a
verifiable Consumer request, you will be asked to provide certain information
to help us verify your identity. The information we ask you to provide to
initiate a request may differ depending upon the type of request, the type,
sensitivity and value of the personal information that is the subject of the
request, and the risk of harm to you that may occur as a result of unauthorized
access or deletion, among other factors. In certain circumstances, we may also
require you to provide a written declaration that you are who you say you are.
You may make a verifiable Consumer request on behalf of your minor child. You may also designate an authorized agent to make a request on your behalf by contacting us at the following toll-free number: 833-978-2139
If we cannot
verify your identity or authority to make the request, we will not be able to
comply with your request. We will inform you if we cannot verify your identity
or authority. We will only use personal information provided in a verifiable
Consumer request to verify the requestor’s identity or authority to make the
request.
How we collect, use and share personal information of Consumers
We have collected the following categories of Personal Information about Consumers in the twelve (12) months prior to the Effective Date of this Policy:
Name, alias, postal address, unique personal identifier, online identifier, Internet Protocol address, email address, account name, social security number, driver’s license number, passport number, or other similar identifiers; Name, signature, social security number, physical characteristics or description, address, telephone number, passport number, driver’s license or state identification card number, insurance policy number, education, employment, employment history, bank account number, credit card number, debit card number, or any other financial information, medical information, or health insurance information;Characteristics of protected classifications under California or federal law (Race, color, national origin, religion, gender, disability (including pregnancy), age (at least 40 years old), citizenship status, sexual orientation, gender identity and gender expression);Commercial information, including records of personal property, products or services purchased, obtained, or considered, or other purchasing or consuming histories or tendencies;Internet or other electronic network activity information, including, but not limited to, browsing history, search history, and information regarding a Consumer’s interaction with an Internet Web site, application, or advertisement; Geolocation data;Audio, electronic, visual, thermal, olfactory, or similar information;Professional or employment-related information;Education information; andInferences drawn from any personal information to create a profile about a Consumer reflecting the Consumer’s preferences, characteristics, psychological trends, predispositions, behavior, attitudes, intelligence, abilities, and aptitudes.
We
collect the personal information described above from the following categories
of sources:
From you directly, when you provide us with information over our websites or in person, in applications or questionnaire responses you submit in connection with one of our products or services, or when you otherwise correspond with one of our employees. From our website analytics providers when you visit our websiteFrom you directly when you are employed by us or as part of our employee recruitment process.From employees of Geller clients, when he or she names you as an emergency contact, beneficiary, additional insured or similar designation.
We collect the
personal information described above for a variety of business purposes. We use
the personal information to:
Provide
our services and activities related to our provision of such services to you, including
maintaining or servicing accounts, providing customer service, verifying
customer information, providing financing, processing payments, processing or
fulfilling transactions that you authorize us to make on your behalf, or providing
analytics services;Maintain
the quality of, and improve, upgrade, or enhance our services to you;Detect
security incidents, protecting against malicious, deceptive, fraudulent, or
illegal activity, and prosecuting those responsible for that activity; andDebug
to identify and repair errors that impair existing functionality.
We may share the
personal information described above with the following categories of third
parties:
We share your personal information
with our service providers to assist us in providing our products and services
to you, including service providers that:provide analytics services to help
us understand the activity on our website;assist us with marketing and
communications with our clients or potential clients;assist us to analyze and understand
the financial status and needs of our client base;assist us with the financial,
regulatory and legal aspects of our business,assist us with quote and estimates
specific to particular individuals interested in our services; andassist us with our data
infrastructure and with data security and privacy.
We have not sold
Personal Information about Consumers in the twelve (12) months prior to the
Effective Date of this Policy.
We have disclosed
Personal Information about Consumers for a business purpose in the twelve (12)
months prior to the Effective Date of this Policy. We have disclosed the
following categories of Personal Information about consumers for a business
purpose in the twelve (12) months prior to the Effective Date of this Policy:
Name, alias, postal address, unique personal identifier, online identifier, Internet Protocol address, email address, account name, social security number, driver’s license number, passport number, or other similar identifiers; Name, signature, social security number, physical characteristics or description, address, telephone number, passport number, driver’s license or state identification card number, insurance policy number, education, employment, employment history, bank account number, credit card number, debit card number, or any other financial information, medical information, or health insurance information; Characteristics of protected classifications under California or federal law (Race, color, national origin, religion, gender (including pregnancy), disability, age (at least 40 years old), citizenship status, sexual orientation, gender identity and gender expression);
Commercial information, including records of personal property, products or services purchased, obtained, or considered, or other purchasing or consuming histories or tendencies.; Professional or employment-related information; and Inferences drawn from any personal information to create a profile about a Consumer reflecting the Consumer’s preferences, characteristics, psychological trends, predispositions, behavior, attitudes, intelligence, abilities, and aptitudes.
Personal Information of Minors
We do not sell
Personal Information about anyone, including, but not limited to, minors under
the age of 16.
Contact for More Information
If
you have any questions or concerns about Geller’s privacy policy and practices,
please contact webmaster@gellerco.com.
Last updated January 1, 2020
